BRAD PRESTON

LOCKSMITH

RESUME OBJECTIVE

I'm a certified locksmith with 1 year of experience working with high security locks, organizing keys in software, and performing daily maintenance on cylinders and hardware. I have worked extensively with the Key Wizard program to issue and document keys. My experience in locksmithing covers residential, commercial, high security, and some automotive locks.

EXPERIENCE

Locksmith

Presidential Safe and Security, Kalamazoo, MI | January 2019 - Present

- Cut new or duplicate keys and stamp with the appropriate identification
- Work closely with security personnel to assure that all locks are working and working well
- Pin new cores with the appropriate pin stack for the keys required to have access to the room
- Maintain discretion when dealing with high security locks and the master key system
- Disassemble locks to repair and replace worn tumblers, springs, and other parts

Trim Carpenter

JB Preston Construction, Vicksburg, MI | March 2018 - January 2019

- Cut trim safely using a miter saw, table saw, jigsaw or coping saw
- Read kitchen and bathroom plans for installing cabinets and building built-in shelves/storage
- Installed trim around doors and windows assuring that the joints were properly aligned
- Installed baseboard so it sits nicely on the floor and corners were appropriately aligned
- Provided solutions for clients when unexpected issues arose

Night Stock

Family Fare, Vicksburg, MI | January 2018 - March 2018

- Served customers with a friendly attitude and assisted them with excellent service.
- Loaded and organized shelves and assisted with setting up displays
- Maintained a clean and organized environment for the safety of customers and employees
- Read labels and checked products to ensure that no outdated or damaged products were placed on the shelves

Carpenter

JB Preston Construction, Vicksburg, MI | May 2011 – January 2018

- Read blueprints and building plans to assure that the house is being framed properly
- Installed doors and windows
- Measured, cut, and shape wood according to the blueprints
- Constructed frameworks such as walls, floors, door frames, and window frames
- Inspected and replaced damaged or broken framework
- Kept the job site clean and organized to ensure the safety of employees
- Installed siding and shingles

bap5393@gmail.com

(269) 823-2628

7998 Hope Street Vicksburg, MI 49097

SKILLS

Detail Oriented

Adaptable

Strong Work Ethic

Organized

Creative

Desire to Learn

EDUCATION

Vicksburg High School

501 E Hwy Street Vicksburg, MI 49097 Graduated 2011

Lockmasters Security Institute

2101 John C Watts Dr Nicholasville , KY 40356 Completed March 2019

LICENSES AND CERTIFICATIONS

Professional Locksmithing

2019

Simplex

2019

Medeco

2019

*References available upon request